Finding Aid for Athletic Department (University of Michigan) records, 1860-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sports Information Office, 1860-
  - Track-women
    - Photographs
      - Portraits and Action Shots
        - 2 006/06
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships 5/12/2006-5/14/2006, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - James Henry Family photo (Box 262)
        - 2006/07
          - 2007 Team and group photo and some headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - 2007 Player headshots, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
            (one cd has files named with athlete names)
          - Women's Track Hall of Fame Induction 1/20/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Red Simmons/Jack Harvey Invitational 1/19/2007-1/20/2007, 4 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Silverston Invitational 2/16/2007, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - EMU Twilight Invitational 4/20/2007, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Penn Relays 4/26/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Len Paddock Invitational 5/4/2007-5/5/2007, 4 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships 5/11/2007-5/13/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
        - 2007/2008
          - 2007 Team photos(with some headshots and posed action), 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - 2007 Headshots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Michigan Intercollegiate Invitational 2/1/2008-2/2/2008, 4 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - EMU Classic 2/16/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Big Ten Indoor Championships 3/1/2008-3/2/2008, 2 optical disks DVDs (Box 262)
          - NCAA Indoor Championship 3/14/2008-3/15/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Central Collegiate Meet (At EMU) 1/9/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Penn Relays, 4/242008-4/28/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Len Paddock, 5/92008-5/10/2008, 4 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - Big Ten Outdoor Championships 5/16/2008-5/18/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - NCAA Outdoor Championships 6/11/2008-6/14/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
          - NCAA Outdoor Championships 6/11/2008-6/14/2008, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 262)
            [Copyright Errol Anderson]
    - Results
      - 1976-1977 (Box 71)
      - 1977/78 (Box 71)
      - 1978/79
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1979/80
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1980/81
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1981/82
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1982/83
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1983/84
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1984/85
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1985/86
        - Indoor (Box 71)
      - 1986/87
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1987/88
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1988/89
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1989/90
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - 1990/91
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Releases and Miscellaneous (Box 71)
      - 1991/92 (Box 71)
      - 1992/93
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 71)
      - 1993/94
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 71)
        - Clippings/News releases (Box 71)
      - 1994/95
        - Indoor (Box 71)
        - Outdoor (Box 71)
      - 1995/96
        - Indoor (Box 211)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 211)
        - News releases and Articles (Box 211)
      - 1996/97
        - Indoor (Box 211)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 211)
      - 1997/98
        - Indoor (Box 211)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 211)
        - Clippings (Box 211)
      - 1998/99
        - Indoor (Box 211)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 211)
        - Clippings (Box 211)
      - 1999/2000
        - Results, 3 folders (Box 211)
        - News Releases (Box 212)
        - Post Event (Box 212)
      - 2000/01
        - Results, 2 folders (Box 212)
        - News Clippings (Box 212)
        - News Releases (Box 212)
      - 2001/02
        - Indoor (Box 212)
        - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box 212)
        - News Clips (Box 285)
        - Releases, Post-event (Box 285)
        - Releases, Weekly (Box 285)
        - Season Bests (Box 285)
      - 2002/03
        - Regular Season, 2 folders (Box 285)
        - Post Season, Indoor (Box 285)
        - Post Season, Outdoor (Box 285)
        - Season in Review (Box 285)
      - 2003/04
        - Indoor (Box 285)
        - outdoor (Box 285)
        - Season ion review (Box 285)
      - 2004/05
        - Indoor (Box 285)
        - Outdoor (Box 285)
        - Season in Review (Box 285)
        - Clippings (Box 284)
        - Clippings (Box 285)
        - NCAA "Track Wire" (Box 284)
        - Drake relays Program (Box 284)
          (several feature on U-M athletes)
      - 2006
        - Season in Review (Box 284)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Compiled U-M records by event, as of 2004 (Box 241)
      - Big Ten record book, 2004-05 (Box 241)
  - Volleyball
    - Media Guides
      - 1978, 1981-1983, 1985-1992 (Box 155)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 155)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 155)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 155)
      - 2000 (Box 155)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 155)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 155)
      - 2005 (Box 155)
      - 2008 (Box 155)
      - Big Ten Media Guide 1996-1996 (Box 155)
    - Historical Statistics and Miscellaneous
      - History (Box 155)
        (includes records, honors, and stats over time)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 155)
        (includes blank statistics forms, volleyball playing guides, fan's letter to Greg Giovanazzi)
    - Programs
      - 1973-1975 (Box 155)
      - 1980-1984 (Box 155)
      - 1988-1991 (Box 155)
      - 1992-1996 (Box 155)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 155)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 155)
    - Photographs
      - Team Photos (Box 156)
        - 1977-1993 (Box 156)
        - 1994-2001, 2003 (Box 156)
      - Coaches (Box 156)
      - Portraits and Action Shots
        - 1977-1983 (Box 156)
        - 1984-1987 (Box 156)
        - 1988/89 (Box 156)
        - 1989/90 (Box 156)
        - 1990/91 (Box 156)
        - 1991/92, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - 1992/93, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - 1993/94, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - 1994/1995 (Box 156)
        - 1995/1996 (Box 156)
        - 1996/1997, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - 1997/1998, 4 folders (Box 156)
        - 1998/1999, 3 folders (Box 156)
        - 1999/2000, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - 2000/2001, 2 folders (Box 157)
        - 2001/2002 (Box 157)
        - Miscellaneous unidentified photos, 2 folders (Box 157)
        - 2002/2003 (Box 157)
        - 2007 Individual Player Cards (picture & stats) (Box 157)
        - 2008 Souvenir Photo Book (Box 157)
      - Photos and miscellaneous 1977-1996, 1 volumes (Box 230)
        (contact sheet of team and individual players, some Kalmbach action c/s, team photo captions, picture day captions)
      - Randy Mascharka Photographs
        - 1991, slides, 1 binder (Box 230)
        - 1992, slides, 1 binder (Box 230)
        - 1995-1997, negs/cs, 1 binder (Box 230)
      - Digital Media
        - 2002-2003 (digital files of media guides, headshots and team photos, game action, media files) (Box 231)
        - 2004 (contact sheets & digital files of media guide, headshots and team photos, game action.) (Box 231)
        - 2005 (contact sheets & digital files of headshots and team photos, game action) (Box 231)
        - 2006 (contact sheets & digital files of headshots and team, game action, NCAA game action) (Box 231)
        - 2007 (digital files and contact sheets of media guides, game action, team photos, headshots) (Box 231)
        - 2008 (digital files and contact sheets of media day, team photos, NCAA game action, game action) (Box 231)
        - 2008 DVDs (digital film, 2008 highlight video and 2008 seniors speak about the team) (Box 231)
        - 2009 Pictures for Locker Room (Box 231)
    - Press Releases & Clippings
      - 1990/1991 (Box 157)
      - 1991/1992 (Box 157)
      - 1992/1993 (Box 157)
      - 1993/1994 (Box 157)
      - 1994/1995 (Box 157)
      - 1995/1996 (Box 157)
      - 1996/1997, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - 1997/1998, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - 1998/1999, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - 1999/2000, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - 2000/2001, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - 2001/2002 (Box 157)
      - 2002 (Box 157)
    - Results
      - 1977-1980 (Box 158)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 158)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 158)
      - 1986 (Box 158)
      - 1987 (Box 158)
      - 1988 (Box 158)
      - 1989 (Box 158)
      - 1990
        - Regular season (Box 158)
        - Big Ten Conference (Box 158)
      - 1991 (Box 158)
      - 1992
        - Regular season (Box 158)
        - AVCA polls (Box 158)
        - Big Ten Conference (Box 158)
        - NCAA Tournament (Box 158)
      - 1993 (Box 158)
      - 1995 (Box 158)
      - 1996
        - Regular season (Box 158)
        - Big Ten Conference (Box 158)
        - Regular season (Box 158)
        - Big Ten Conference (Box 158)
      - 1998
        - Regular season (Box 158)
        - AVCA polls (Box 158)
        - Big Ten Conference (Box 158)
      - 1999
        - Regular season, 2 folders (Box 159)
        - AVCA polls (Box 159)
        - Big Ten Conference (Box 159)
        - NCAA Tournament (Box 159)
      - 2000
        - Regular season (Box 159)
        - AVCA polls & Big Ten Conference (Box 159)
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box 159)
      - Special Events
        - "Rock the House" event: 1992-1998 (Box 159)
        - "State Pride" Match: 1990-1998 (Box 159)
        - Volleyball Challenge
          - 1993-1998 (Box 159)
          - 1999-2000 (Box 159)
          - 2008, 2 folders (Box 159)
          - 2009 (Season Recap), 2 folders (Box 159)
  - Water Polo
    - Media Guides
      - 2001-2003 (Box 222)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 222)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 222)
      - 2008-2009 (Box 222)
    - Results and Statistics
      - 2001 (Box 222)
      - 2002 (Box 222)
      - 2003 (Box 222)
      - 2004, 2 folders (Box 222)
      - 2005 (Box 222)
      - 2005 (NCAA Championships hosted by U-M) (Box 222)
      - 2006 (Box 283)
      - 2007 (Box 283)
      - 2008 (Box 283)
      - 2009 (Box 283)
      - 2010 (Box 283)
      - 2011 (Box 283)
      - Statistical History 2001-2009 (Box 283)
    - Programs and Post-Season Guides
      - 2001 (Box 222)
      - 2002 (Box 222)
      - 2003 (Box 222)
      - 2004 (Box 222)
      - 2005 (Box 222)
      - 2008 (Box 283)
      - 2009 (Box 283)
      - 2010 (Box 283)
      - 2011 (Box 283)
    - Press Releases and Articles
      - 2001 (Box 222)
      - 2002 (Box 222)
      - 2003, 2 folders (Box 222)
      - 2004, 2 folders (Box 222)
      - 2005 (Box 222)
      - 2008 (Box 222)
      - 2006 (Box 283)
      - 2008 (Box 283)
    - Photos
      - Portraits and Action
        - 2000/01, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          (media guide file, low res had and action shots)
        - 201/02
          - Team Photo and headshots (Box 223)
          - 2002 Pics, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
            (low res team and headshots)
          - Intra-squad (?) 10/15/2001, 1/15/2002 (Box 223)
          - Michigan State 3/15/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - NCAA, Stanford 5/11/2003, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - NCAA Loyola Marymount, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Media Guide Files, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
        - 2003/04
          - Headshots, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - 2003 Pics / Compiled action shots by player, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - San Jose State 1/26/2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Eastern Michigan 1/26/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Penn State-Behrend, Washington and Jefferson 3/9/2004, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - 2003 Archive, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
            (results, stats, player bios, game stories and releases, media guide files
          - 2003 Media Guide, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
        - 2004/05
          - Head shots, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
            (also includes some track headshots)
          - Colorado State and Indiana 1/29/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Indiana 3/18/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Loyola Marymount 3/18/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Wheaton and LMK 3/18/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Brown and Senior Day 2/20/2005, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - NCAA Championship Meet 5/13/2005-5/15/2005, 3 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
        - 2005/06
          - Team and headshots, 2 optical disks CDs; cs (Box 223)
          - Long Beach St., Colorado, Indiana 2/4/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Cal-San Diego, Slippery Rock 2/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Indiana 3/17/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - California Baptist and Grove City 3/18/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Cal State-Northridge 3/18/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Michigan State 4/13/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Compiles action shots 2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
        - 2006/07
          - Headshots and Team photos, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Alumni Game 9/23/2006, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Media Guide photos (posed action), 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Indiana 1/27/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Marist 1/27/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Michigan Kickoff day 2 (Colorado State and Santa Cruz 1/28/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Wagner 3/17/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Marymount 3/17/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - California Lutheran 3/18/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Washington and Jefferson,4/21/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Slippery Rock 4/21/2007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Indiana, 4/222007, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
        - 2007/08
          - Team and group photos, headshots, 10/3/2007, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Colorado State 1/26/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Arizona State 1/26/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - UC San Diego, 1/27/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Stanford Invitational, vs Arizona State 2/10/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Wolverine Invitational 3/15/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Indiana 3/17/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Hartwick 3/24/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - 2008 Eastern Championships
            - Mercyhurst 4/24/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
            - Princeton 4/26/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
            - Hartwick 4/27/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
            - NCAA, USC 5/9/2008, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
        - 2008/09
          - Team and group photos and headshots and posed action 11/17/2008, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - California 1/24/2009, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - San Jose State 1/25/2009, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - UCLA 1/25/2009, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - CWPA League games 2/7/2009, 5 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Underwater photos 3/7/2009 (Box 223)
          - Gannon and Mercyhurst 3/13/2009, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
          - Iona and Marist 3/14/2009, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 223)
  - Women's Athletics (All Sports)
    - Media Guides
      - 1975/76, 1977 Fall Sports, 1978 Spring Sports, 1981/82 Winter Sports (Box 81-A)
  - All-Sports
    - M Magazine
      - 2004/05 (Box 81-A)
      - 2005/06 (Box 81-A)
      - 2006/07 (Box 81-A)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Tickets, Schedules etc.
      - Scrapbook, ca. 1898- circa 1911 (Volume 1)
        (includes ticket books, game passes, schedules, etc. for football, baseball, and track; also Athletic Association rule books and membership cards)
      - Pocket Schedule Cards
        - 1931-1969 (Box 80)
        - 1969/70-1993/94 (Box 80)
        - 1994/95-2003/04 (Box 80)
        - 2005/06 (Box 80)
      - Posters / Schedules
        - Football (Folder 1)
        - Baseball and Basketball (Folder 2)
        - Hockey and wrestling (Folder 3)
        - Other Men's sports (Folder 4)
        - Women's sports, basketball-rowing (Folder 5)
        - Women's sports, soccer-water polo (Folder 6)
    - Publications, Brochures, etc.
      - "All Sports Review" (Box 46)
        (Team and individual results, statistics, honors, etc.)
        - 1989/90-1992/93 (Box 46)
        - 1993/94-1994/95 (Box 46)
      - 1898 Chicago Game (Box 46)
        (newspaper articles re. game and writing of "The Victors")
      - 1898 Football Team 40 Year Reunion (Box 46)
      - 1940 California game-Tom Harmon (Box 12)
        (Clippings from San Francisco newspapers including pictures of the "12th man" incident, clippings by Louis Flora, father of Bob Flora, also several photos of Bob and Louis Flora)
      - "Blue Magic" (Box 46)
        (script for TV show on Michigan Football history, 1979)
      - Campus Information for Athletes (Box 46)
      - Correspondence re: "100 Years of Michigan Athletics" 1937 (Box 46)
      - Detroit Lions vs. Cleveland Browns at Michigan Stadium 1971 (Box 46)
      - Heisman Trophy Award Program 1991 (Desmond Howard) (Box 46)
      - Hockey ephemera (Box 46)
        (includes. Felsner card)
      - "Jim Hunt, University of Michigan Trainer" (Box 46)
      - Jim Thorpe Award Program 1997 Charles Woodson (Box 46)
      - Lawton, J. Fred, Poems etc. (Box 46)
      - Lists of conference and NCAA champions, all-conference and all-American athletes, 1879-1974. (Box 46)
      - Longman, Frank "Shorty", Biographical sketch by Dick Kispaugh (Box 46)
      - Magazine Covers featuring UM Athletes (Harmon, Chappuis, Oosterbaan, Ortmann) (Box 46)
        (also box 12)
      - "Michigan Football Review" 1947 and 1948 seasons (Box 46)
      - "Michigan in Western Conference Athletics," 1923 (Box 46)
      - Olympic Games
        (U.S. and International Olympic Committee publications, include photos and information on UM athletes)
        - 1948 Swimming Trials (Detroit) (Box 46)
        - The Olympian, November 1984 (results of 1984 games) (Box 46)
        - 1964 score card (Box 46)
        - 1968 USOC Program (Box 46)
        - 1984 US basketball trials (Box 46)
      - "One Hundred Years of Michigan Football" (Ann Arbor News supplement, 1979) (Box 46)
      - Recruiting Brochures (All Sports) 1970, 1979 (Box 46)
      - Schembechler, Glen
        - "20 Years-20 Teams: Our Tribute to Bo" 1989 (Box 46)
        - "Bo The End of an Era" (1990 ?) (Box 46)
        - "A Salute To Bo" May 6, 1990 (Box 46)
      - Sigma Chi Football Banquet 1927 (Box 46)
      - Student Services Newsletter 1991 (Box 46)
      - Walter Camp Awards Program 1970 (Box 46)
        (Schembechler coach of the year)
      - Yost Award Banquet Programs (Box 46)
      - "Yost A Michigan Institution" (Box 46)
        (from 1940 "Toast to Yost from Coast to Coast")
      - Football Charts (Box 4)
        (oversize charts prepared by Earl Riskey giving football season summaries, captains, All-Americans, etc., 1879-1973)
      - Michigan Daily Photo Supplement May 26, 1922 (Box 9)
        (Spring sports photos)
      - Scrapbook 1894 (Box 12)
        (copy of Detroit Free Press articles on the 1894 Cornell football game and article on 1891 Cornell game)
      - Football team "calendars" with portraits of players 1901-1904 (Box 12)
      - Football Calendars (Signature Sports) 1996, 1997, 1998 (Box 12)
      - All Sports Calendar 1911 (Box 12)
      - USSR Gymnastics Tour December 12, 1976 (Box 12)
      - ESPN Magazine, "One Day, One Game," March 13, 2013 (Box 13)
        (Feature stories on events surrounding 2013 Michigan-Ohio State basketball game)
      - Sports Illustrated 25th Anniversary Issue 1979 (Box 13)
        (covers of SI from 8/1955 to 12/1978. Accompanying note by Moby Benedict lists all the U-M athletes on covers.)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings (Folder 10)
        (full page stories and special editions, includes 1998 Hockey NCAA championship (M Daily), 2005 Softball NCAA Championship (M Daily), 1948 Rose Bowl (L.A. Examiner) Big Ten Centennial (Chicago Tribune); 2006 UM-OSU game)
    - Les Etter files 1922-1964
      - Articles (reprints and typescripts)
        - Ann Arbor Sports Bureau (Box 46)
          (articles and press releases written by Mill Marsh, May-August 1938)
        - "The Tradition That Is Michigan" (Box 46)
          (reprint of article from College Football Illustrated, ca. 1947)
        - "A Brief History of Intercollegiate Athletics at Michigan" (Box 46)
          (2 versions)
        - "Athletics at the University of Michigan" (Box 46)
        - "The Board in Control Physical Education" (Box 46)
        - "University of Michigan Athletic Plant" (Box 46)
      - Correspondence, Clippings, Reports
        - 1925, 1926 (Box 46)
          (incl. copy of 1926 "Report on University Athletics")
      - 1898 Football Team Reunion, 1938 (Box 46)
      - 150 lb. football 1947-1948 (photos) (Box 46)
      - UM All-Americans (Box 46)
        (Correspondence 1960-1962 and biographical information on UM all-American players and drafts of articles on them for 1962 ? football programs)
    - Releases
      - Miscellaneous files (Box 46)
        (includes memos, reports, text for press releases)
      - Crisler Arena (Box 46)
        (Dedication program, press releases, etc.)
    - Centennial Committee 1979
      - Millie Schembechler files (Box 46)
    - Photographs
      - Athletic Facilities (non football)
        - Athletic Campus aerials (Box 80)
        - Administration Building (Hartwig Building) (Box 80)
        - Athletic Academic Center, Ground Breaking May 13, 2004, 110 images on 1 CD (Box 80)
        - Baseball Field (construction, ca. 1921) (Box 80)
        - Canham Natatorium construction, 2 folders (Box 80)
        - Cliff Keen Arena (Box 80)
        - Crisler Arena (Box 80)
          (including locker rooms and trainers facilities)
        - Golf Course and Club House (Box 80)
          (see also outsize folder Fimul F84)
        - Intra-Mural Sports Building, color transparency (Box 80)
        - Pools (Michigan Union, Matt Mann, Canham Natatorium) (Box 80)
        - Track and Tennis Building (Box 80)
        - Yost Field House (Box 80)
    - Photographs
      - Athletic Directors
        - Baird, Barthelme, Yost, Crisler, Canham, Schembechler, Weidenbach (Box 80)
      - Coach and Staff portraits circa 1970-1980
        (negs. with some contact prints)
        - A-L (Box 80)
          (Abraham, R. Anderson, Anton, Atwood, Bahr, Bay, Benedict, Bleznak, Borders, Boyce, Brown, Brummett, Burton, Campbell, Canham, Carr, Carter, Collins, Cornell, Cusumano, Duford, Dutcher, Eisner, Fagan, Falk, Farley, Farrel, Fife, Gadson, Gittleson, Green, Hanlon, Harbaugh, Harris, Hartwig, Harvey, Henry, Hinton, Hoey, Hughes, Hunt, Hyatt, Isaac, Jenkins, Jochin, Johannsen, Kimball, Lindeman, Lokken)
        - M-Y (Box 80)
          (Madej, Martin, McCartney, McLean, Meter, Middaugh, Miller, Nehlen, Newcomb, Ocker, O'Connor, Owens, Palmisano, P. Perry, W. Perry, Pierson, Ponto, Reed, Renfrew, Robey, M. Schembechler, Schudel, Schwartz, Seyferth, Shepard, Simmons, Simon, Smith, Snyder, Stager, Steffen, Stevenson, Stobart, Swiss, Syphax, Thornblad, Uriah, Voletich, Ruegink, Uzelac, Vong, Warhurst, Young)
        - Phyllis Ocker (Box 14)
    - Photographs
      - Miscellaneous Photos